In this video we're going to wrap up our series on type checking with a discussion
在这段视频中，我们将用一个讨论来结束我们关于类型检查的系列
of how to recover from type errors. So as with all the other front end phases, like
如何从类型错误中恢复。就像所有其他前端阶段一样，比如
flexing and parsing, it's important to recover from errors that happen during
灵活处理和解析，重要的是要从以下过程中发生的错误中恢复
type checking But unlike parsing, it's much, much easier to recover from errors
类型检查，但与解析不同，从错误中恢复要容易得多
in the type checker because we already have the up stacks and text tree and so
在类型检查器中，因为我们已经有了上行堆栈和文本树，所以
there's no need to skip over portions of the code as we did in parsing before we
不需要像我们在解析之前那样跳过部分代码
even knew what the structure of the program was. The problem though, is what
甚至知道节目的结构是什么。但问题是，
type should we assign to an expression that has no legitimate type? The type
类型是否应该赋给没有合法类型的表达式？类型
checker works by structural induction, and it can't just get stuck. So if we find
Checker的工作原理是结构归纳，它不能就这样卡住。所以如果我们发现
some sub expression that has no type that we can meaningfully give it, we still have
一些子表达式没有我们可以有意义地赋予它类型，我们仍然有
to do something with it so that we can type check all the expressions that
要对其执行某些操作，以便我们可以键入，请选中所有符合以下条件的表达式
surround it. One possibility is to simply assign the type object as the type of any
包围它。一种可能是简单地将类型Object指定为任何
ill typed expression. And the intuition here is that even if we couldn't figure
键入的表达式不正确。这里的直觉是即使我们不知道
out what the type or the expression was supposed to be, certainly it was something
从这个类型或表达应该是什么，它肯定是什么东西
that was a sub type of object. So it is certainly safe to assign any expression
那是一种亚类型的物体。因此，将任何表达式赋值给
the type object. So let's consider what happens with this strategy in a simple
类型对象。那么让我们简单地考虑一下这个策略会发生什么
piece of code. So here we have a little code fragment and we just assume here that
一段代码。所以在这里我们有一小段代码，我们在这里只是假设
X is undefined, that actually there's a bug in this code and that's at X has no
X是未定义的，实际上在这段代码中有一个错误，那就是X没有
binding. So there's no type anywhere for X. So what happens when we type check
有约束力的。所以任何地方都没有X的类型。那么当我们输入check时会发生什么呢？
this? Well, we're going to recursively walk down the abstract syntax tree,
这?好的，我们将沿着抽象语法树递归遍历，
eventually we'll get to the leaves, and we'll try to type check X. And then we'll
最终我们将到达树叶，我们将尝试键入check X，然后我们将
discover that there is no type for X anywhere and that will result in an error
发现没有X Anywhere的类型，这将导致错误
message Saying that X is undefined And then in order to proceed with type
消息称X未定义，然后为了继续键入
checking, in order to recover, we'll have to assign X a type And so, we'll just
正在检查，为了恢复，我们必须给X赋值一个类型，因此，我们只需
assume that X has type object, because that's our recovery strategy And now we'll
假设X具有Object类型，因为这是我们的恢复策略，现在我们将
continue to type check as we walk up the abstr act syntax tree, and the next thing
当我们沿着abstr act语法树向上移动时，继续键入check，然后进行下一步操作
we'll try to do is to type check this plus operation. We'll see that we're adding
我们要做的就是键入check this加号运算。我们将看到我们正在添加
something of type object to, an integer. And of course plus doesn't work on things
Object to类型的东西，一个整数。当然，PLUS对某些事情不起作用
of type object, so we'll get an error. Something like plus applied to an object.
类型为Object，所以我们会得到一个错误。适用于物体的类似加号的东西。
And then we'll have to decide, now that we couldn't type check this plus, what the
然后我们必须决定，既然我们不能输入check this加号，那么
type is of X+2, so this whole sub-expression and of course our recovery
类型是X+2，所以整个子表达式，当然还有我们的恢复
strategy is to say, well that also has type object And now the next thing up in
策略是这样说的，也有Object类型，现在下一件事是
the abstract syntax tree is this initialization assignment. Here we're
抽象语法树就是这个初始化赋值。我们在这里
assigning Y the result of this expression But we couldn't type check this expression
将此表达式的结果赋给Y，但我们无法键入check this表达式
so it has type object And now the type checker sees that we're assigning
所以它有类型对象，现在类型检查器看到我们正在分配
something of type object to something of type int and we get yet a third
类型为Object的对象类型为int类型的对象，并且我们还获得了第三个
error Saying that we have a bad assignment, of some kind. So The nut of
错误地说我们有一项糟糕的任务，某种形式的。所以这颗坚果
the, the problem here is that this simple recovery strategy works. If we do recover
这里的问题是，这个简单的恢复策略是有效的。如果我们真的恢复了
we continue type checking. But a single error leads potentially to, lots of other
我们继续进行类型检查。但一个单一的错误可能会导致许多其他的错误
errors. So this is a workable solution. It, it, it achieves the goal of recovering
错误。所以这是一个可行的解决方案。它，它，它达到了恢复的目的
But in general it will lead, to cascading errors. Once you have on one type error
但一般来说，它会导致级联错误。一旦你有一个打字错误
that type error will just cause many more because not very many things can be done
该类型错误只会导致更多错误，因为可以做的事情不是很多
with something of type object And probably the code was written assuming some more
具有Object类型的内容，并且很可能代码是假设更多的内容编写的
specific type And these errors will just propagate up the abstract syntax tree
特定类型，并且这些错误只会向上传播抽象语法树
until some point just result in multiple errors Another possibility is to introduce
直到某一点只会导致多个错误，另一种可能是引入
a new type, a No type that is specifically for use with ill typed expressions And No
一个新类型、一个专门用于错误类型表达式的No类型和No
type is very special. It's not a type that is available to the programmer. It's only
类型是非常特殊的。它不是程序员可用的类型。它只是
available to the compiler and it's just there for error recovery and type
可供编译器使用，它仅用于错误恢复和键入
checking. And the special property of No type is that it's going to be a sub type
正在检查。No type的特殊属性是它将是一个子类型
of every other type. So if you remember object was the opposite. Object is a super
所有其他类型的。所以如果你记得，物体是相反的。对象是一个超级
type of every type and that had the bad property that there are very
每种类型的类型，都有非常糟糕的属性
few methods that defined on object and so if you plug in type object. Where you
在Object上定义的方法很少，所以如果您插入类型Object。你在哪里
expected some other type probably it's not going to type check. So we can fix that
需要其他类型，可能不会进行类型检查。所以我们可以解决这个问题
problem by introducing no type. And no type will have this special property that
通过引入无类型来解决问题。任何类型都不会有这样的特殊属性
every operation, every operation is defined for no type And furthermore we'll
每个操作，每个操作都没有定义类型，而且我们将
say that it produces no type as a result. So any operation in the language that
假设结果是它不生成类型。所以语言中的任何操作
takes an argument of type no type it will produce a result of type no type. So the
接受类型为no类型的参数，它将产生类型为no类型的结果。因此，
no types will propagate. And now let's take a look at our same code fragment and
不会传播任何类型。现在让我们看一下我们相同的代码片段
let's work through what happens if we use no type. So, again we walk down the
让我们研究一下如果不使用类型会发生什么。所以，我们再一次沿着
abstract syntax tree we get to this leaf X, we see that X is undefined, we
抽象语法树我们到达这个叶X，我们看到X是未定义的，我们
produce an error saying X is undefined. And then we have to assign a type to X so
产生一个错误，指出X是未定义的。然后我们必须给X赋值一个类型，所以
we say well X has type no type and now we consider the plus operation And now plus
我们说X有类型，没有类型，现在我们考虑加号运算，现在是加号
is taking an augmentative type no type integer And this is fine. We're not gonna
采用的是加法类型，不是整数类型，这是可以接受的。我们不会
produce any errors that's consider to be well type and the results is also of type
产生任何被认为是良好类型的错误，并且结果也是类型
no type. And now we're doing an assignment And no type is compatible with N. No type
没有类型。现在我们正在进行赋值，没有类型与N兼容，没有类型
is a subtype of N. So this assignment is also type correct And we don't produce any
是N的子类型，所以这个赋值也是类型正确的，我们不生成任何
type of error in that stage either And so, you can see what happens here is that no
这一阶段的错误类型也是如此，因此，您可以看到这里发生的情况是没有
types propagate up the abstract syntax tree just like the object types did before
类型在抽象语法树中向上传播，就像以前的对象类型一样
But since no type is a special type it's used only for error recovery. We can
但是，因为没有类型是特殊类型，所以它只用于错误恢复。我们可以的
distinguish it from all the other regular types And we know that we shouldn't print
将它与所有其他常规类型区分开来，我们知道不应该打印
out an error message after the first one is produced. So a real compiler, a
在生成第一个错误消息后发出错误消息。所以一个真正的编译器，一个
production compiler would use something like no type, for error recovery But there
生产编译器将使用类似于无类型的东西来进行错误恢复，但是
is an implementation issue with no type. And in particular, the fact that no type
是一个没有类型的实现问题。特别值得一提的是，没有任何类型
is a subtype of every other class means that the class hierarchy is no longer a
是每个其他类的子类型意味着类层次结构不再是
tree. If you think about it, you have object at the top and then you have this
树。如果你想一想，你在顶部有一个物体，然后你就有了这个
tree structure branching out. But then no type is a subtype of everything. So no
树状结构向外分枝。但是没有一种类型是万事万物的子类型。所以不是
type becomes a bottom ele ment And This is now a DAG and not a tree, and that makes
类型变成了底部元素，这现在是DAG而不是树，这使得
it just slightly harder to implement. Instead of being able to just have tree
只是实施起来稍微困难一点。而不是只有一棵树
algorithms now you have to have either have a special case for no type or just do
算法现在你必须有一个没有类型的特殊情况，或者干脆这样做
something more general. And this is just enough extra hassle that I personally
一些更笼统的东西。这已经够多的额外麻烦了，我个人
don't think it's worth doing for the course project and I recommend that you
我认为这不值得为课程项目做这件事，我建议你
use the object solution and we just live with the propagating, or compounding,
使用对象解决方案，我们只需忍受传播，或复合，
errors that, that produces.
由此产生的错误。